[
  {
    "name": "venusaur-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Venusaur",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10033.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10033.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "grass",
      "poison"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 123,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 122,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "charizard-mega-x",
    "mega_name": "Mega Charizard X",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10034.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10034.gif",
    "maxHP": 214,
    "currentHP": 214,
    "types": [
      "fire",
      "dragon"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 78,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 111,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "charizard-mega-y",
    "mega_name": "Mega Charizard Y",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10035.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10035.gif",
    "maxHP": 214,
    "currentHP": 214,
    "types": [
      "fire",
      "flying"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 78,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 104,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 78,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 159,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "blastoise-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Blastoise",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10036.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10036.gif",
    "maxHP": 216,
    "currentHP": 216,
    "types": [
      "water"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 79,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 103,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 135,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 78,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "beedrill-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Beedrill",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10090.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10090.gif",
    "maxHP": 194,
    "currentHP": 194,
    "types": [
      "bug",
      "poison"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 40,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 15,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "pidgeot-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Pidgeot",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10073.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10073.gif",
    "maxHP": 222,
    "currentHP": 222,
    "types": [
      "normal",
      "flying"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 83,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 135,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 121,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "alakazam-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Alakazam",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10037.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10037.gif",
    "maxHP": 178,
    "currentHP": 178,
    "types": [
      "psychic"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 55,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 50,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 175,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "slowbro-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Slowbro",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10071.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10071.gif",
    "maxHP": 242,
    "currentHP": 242,
    "types": [
      "water",
      "psychic"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 180,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 30,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "gengar-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Gengar",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10038.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10038.gif",
    "maxHP": 186,
    "currentHP": 186,
    "types": [
      "ghost",
      "poison"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 60,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 170,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "kangaskhan-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Kangaskhan",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10039.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10039.gif",
    "maxHP": 258,
    "currentHP": 258,
    "types": [
      "normal"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 125,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 60,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "pinsir-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Pinsir",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10040.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10040.gif",
    "maxHP": 194,
    "currentHP": 194,
    "types": [
      "bug",
      "flying"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 155,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 90,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "gyarados-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Gyarados",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10041.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10041.gif",
    "maxHP": 242,
    "currentHP": 242,
    "types": [
      "water",
      "dark"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 155,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 109,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 81,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "aerodactyl-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Aerodactyl",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10042.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10042.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "rock",
      "flying"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 135,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "mewtwo-mega-x",
    "mega_name": "Mega Mewtwo X",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10043.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10043.gif",
    "maxHP": 259,
    "currentHP": 259,
    "types": [
      "psychic",
      "fighting"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 106,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 190,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 154,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "mewtwo-mega-y",
    "mega_name": "Mega Mewtwo Y",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10044.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10044.gif",
    "maxHP": 259,
    "currentHP": 259,
    "types": [
      "psychic"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 106,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 194,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 140,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "ampharos-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Ampharos",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10045.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10045.gif",
    "maxHP": 234,
    "currentHP": 234,
    "types": [
      "electric",
      "dragon"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 90,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 165,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 45,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "steelix-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Steelix",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10072.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10072.gif",
    "maxHP": 210,
    "currentHP": 210,
    "types": [
      "steel",
      "ground"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 125,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 230,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 55,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 30,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "scizor-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Scizor",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10046.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10046.gif",
    "maxHP": 202,
    "currentHP": 202,
    "types": [
      "bug",
      "steel"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 140,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "heracross-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Heracross",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10047.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10047.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "bug",
      "fighting"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 185,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 40,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "houndoom-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Houndoom",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10048.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10048.gif",
    "maxHP": 210,
    "currentHP": 210,
    "types": [
      "dark",
      "fire"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 90,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 90,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 140,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 90,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "tyranitar-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Tyranitar",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10049.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10049.gif",
    "maxHP": 250,
    "currentHP": 250,
    "types": [
      "rock",
      "dark"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 164,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 71,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "sceptile-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Sceptile",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10065.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10065.gif",
    "maxHP": 202,
    "currentHP": 202,
    "types": [
      "grass",
      "dragon"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "blaziken-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Blaziken",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10050.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10050.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "fire",
      "fighting"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 160,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "swampert-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Swampert",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10064.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10064.gif",
    "maxHP": 250,
    "currentHP": 250,
    "types": [
      "water",
      "ground"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "gardevoir-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Gardevoir",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10051.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10051.gif",
    "maxHP": 198,
    "currentHP": 198,
    "types": [
      "psychic",
      "fairy"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 68,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 165,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 135,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "sableye-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Sableye",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10066.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10066.gif",
    "maxHP": 170,
    "currentHP": 170,
    "types": [
      "dark",
      "ghost"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 50,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 125,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 20,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "mawile-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Mawile",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10052.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10052.gif",
    "maxHP": 170,
    "currentHP": 170,
    "types": [
      "steel",
      "fairy"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 50,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 125,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 55,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 50,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "aggron-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Aggron",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10053.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10053.gif",
    "maxHP": 202,
    "currentHP": 202,
    "types": [
      "steel"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 140,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 230,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 60,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 50,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "medicham-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Medicham",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10054.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10054.gif",
    "maxHP": 186,
    "currentHP": 186,
    "types": [
      "fighting",
      "psychic"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 60,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 85,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "manectric-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Manectric",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10055.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10055.gif",
    "maxHP": 202,
    "currentHP": 202,
    "types": [
      "electric"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 135,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 135,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "sharpedo-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Sharpedo",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10070.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10070.gif",
    "maxHP": 202,
    "currentHP": 202,
    "types": [
      "water",
      "dark"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 140,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "camerupt-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Camerupt",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10087.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10087.gif",
    "maxHP": 202,
    "currentHP": 202,
    "types": [
      "fire",
      "ground"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 20,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "altaria-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Altaria",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10067.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10067.gif",
    "maxHP": 210,
    "currentHP": 210,
    "types": [
      "dragon",
      "fairy"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "banette-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Banette",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10056.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10056.gif",
    "maxHP": 192,
    "currentHP": 192,
    "types": [
      "ghost"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 64,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 165,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 93,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 83,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 75,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "absol-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Absol",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10057.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10057.gif",
    "maxHP": 194,
    "currentHP": 194,
    "types": [
      "dark"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 65,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 60,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 60,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "glalie-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Glalie",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10074.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10074.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "ice"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "salamence-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Salamence",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10089.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10089.gif",
    "maxHP": 242,
    "currentHP": 242,
    "types": [
      "dragon",
      "flying"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 90,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "metagross-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Metagross",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10076.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10076.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "steel",
      "psychic"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 105,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "latias-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Latias",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10062.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10062.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "dragon",
      "psychic"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 140,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 150,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "latios-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Latios",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10063.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10063.gif",
    "maxHP": 218,
    "currentHP": 218,
    "types": [
      "dragon",
      "psychic"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 130,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 160,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "audino-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Audino",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10069.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10069.gif",
    "maxHP": 254,
    "currentHP": 254,
    "types": [
      "normal",
      "fairy"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 103,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 60,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 126,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 80,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 126,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 50,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "diancie-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Diancie",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10075.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10075.gif",
    "maxHP": 170,
    "currentHP": 170,
    "types": [
      "rock",
      "fairy"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 50,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 160,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 160,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 110,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "lucario-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Lucario",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10059.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10059.gif",
    "maxHP": 202,
    "currentHP": 202,
    "types": [
      "fighting",
      "steel"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 88,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 140,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 70,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 112,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "greninja-ash",
    "mega_name": "Greninja Ash",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10117.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10117.gif",
    "maxHP": 205,
    "currentHP": 205,
    "types": [
      "water",
      "dark"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 72,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 145,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 67,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 153,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 71,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 132,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "garchomp-mega",
    "mega_name": "Mega Garchomp",
    "sprite_front": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/10058.gif",
    "sprite_back": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/PokeAPI/sprites/master/sprites/pokemon/other/showdown/back/10058.gif",
    "maxHP": 262,
    "currentHP": 262,
    "types": [
      "dragon",
      "ground"
    ],
    "stats": [
      {
        "name": "hp",
        "base": 108,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "attack",
        "base": 170,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "defense",
        "base": 115,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-attack",
        "base": 120,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "special-defense",
        "base": 95,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "speed",
        "base": 92,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "accuracy",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      },
      {
        "name": "evasion",
        "base": 100,
        "stage": 0
      }
    ]
  }
]